Anas Moner

Front-End Web Developer

A software developer who graduated from Al-Shorouk university, I have a wide set of technical and professional skills in webdevelopment, including proficiency in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, and React.js. My expertise extends to essential skills such asproblem-solving, object-oriented programming (OOP).

ansmoner2000@gmail.com

Al-obour, Egypt

github.com/Anasmoner2022

+201010304960

SKILLS

HTML/CSS

ExpressJS

in linkedin.com/in/anas-moner-606183236

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree in Civil EngineeringAl-Shrouk Academy

07/2018 - 10/2023

Grade: Good

Digital Egypt Pioneers Initiative(DEPI) YAT Learning Centers

05/2024 - Present

Courses

- MERN Stack Proffessional6 Months-Training
- Bussiness English

- Soft Skills

PERSONAL PROJECTS

NoteKeeper (08/2024 - 08/2024) 🗹

 I am created an application to create and update and edit anddelete notes and create dark/light mode and more interstingthings by using ECMA Script and html and css

CRUD App (09/2024 - 09/2024)

 I am created a simple crud applicetion by using node.js andexpress.js and mongodb and multer and other things to enhancemy backend knowladge.

CERTIFICATES

HTML/CSS (08/2024 - 08/2024) 3

Git Basics (09/2024 - 09/2024) 🗗

Advanced JavaScript (09/2024 - 09/2024) 🗹

Asynchronous JavaScript (09/2024 - 09/2024)

TailwindCSS

APIs

OOP

Git/Github

Advanced React (09/2024 - 10/2024) 🗗

WORK EXPERIENCE

SK E-Commerce

Freelancer

10/2024 - Present

create cosmatics ecommerce for client who start her business, i am creating it with my team to create elegant website and dashaboard . githubRebo

E-commarce Admin Dashborad

Graduation Project

10/2024 - 10/2024

we create Mern stack project for create admin dashboard and we target to update it to sell it as a template. FrontEndRebo, BackEndRebo.

LANGUAGES

English

Professional Working Proficiency

Arabic

Native or Bilingual Proficiency